rummyroyal.com 2013-12-25

# Security and Privacy

**Security**  
Protecting the privacy and security of our members is our number one priority at RummyRoyal. While providing our members with a fun, exciting and attractive skill-based online gaming environment, it is important to us to ensure this platform is also safe and secure and that our members' privacy is fully protected at all times. Our security and privacy policies are strictly enforced at all of our sites and those of our partners'. We conduct all our banking and financial affairs in accordance with generally accepted standards of international banking.

 **Privacy Policy**  
We welcome you to RummyRoyal.com. We provide our services subject to the following terms and conditions contained in this privacy notice (the "Privacy Policy"). If you visit or play at RummyRoyal.com and use any current or future Redfinger Trading Limited. (referred to herein as "RummyRoyal") services, you are deemed to have accepted the Privacy Policy and the End User Agreement that appear on the website www.RummyRoyal.com (the "Site") from time to time.  
We appreciate your trust that we will use and share your privacy on the internet carefully and sensibly. The purpose of the Privacy Policy is to enable you to understand how we collect, store, use and safeguard your personal information and your rights in relation to that information. By visiting or playing at RummyRoyal you are accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy.

 **1\. What information is collected and for what purpose**  
As part of the RummyRoyal account (the "Account") opening process, we will ask you to provide us with certain personal information (the "Personal Information"), including name, postal address, e-mail address and password.  
We will use your Personal Information to confirm various financial transactions, to occasionally send you events and news information and to provide you with customer support services. It is very important that you complete the Account details with valid information, since they will be used in the course of validating financial transactions and for the other aforementioned purposes.  
Players are able to change their Account details by selecting the Account option in the downloaded software.

 **2\. Deposit and withdrawal processing**  
To play for real money, players will need to make a deposit. In the course of making a deposit, players will need to provide deposit method information (For example: credit card number). This information in conjunction with your other Personal Information may be used to clear financial transactions executed by you with RummyRoyal. 

**3\. Confidentiality**  
RummyRoyal undertakes substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of the identity, preferences and other information it has collected about individual Players. RummyRoyal will not knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside RummyRoyal, other than to the Player or as described in this Privacy Policy.

You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and player password, including fees charged to your account. You should also take necessary measures to protect your information and unauthorized access to your password and computer. Your RummyRoyal player password is confidential and we recommend that you not divulge it to anyone or enable others to discover it. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your Personal Information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your Account. If you lose control of your Player password, you may lose control over your Personal Information and may be subject to legally binding actions being taken on your behalf. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your Player password.

 **4\. Limits of Confidentiality**  
Due to the existing legal, regulatory and security environment, we may be required, under certain circumstances, to disclose personally identifiable information about its players. Further, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your player identification, name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, e-mail, and company to third party agents of RummyRoyal as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation for fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, other unlawful activities or any activity whatsoever that may expose us to legal liability.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other Personal Information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in the Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose Personal Information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your Personal Information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information or private communications will always remain private.

 **5\. Who receives your information?**  
In addition to legally required disclosures as explained above, we may disclose your Personal Information to our employees, employees of other companies related to or affiliated with RummyRoyal and to third party service providers who use your Personal Information to provide services to us in respect of you being a player with RummyRoyal. All parties who come into possession of your Personal Information under this provision shall be bound by applicable data protection laws to keep your Personal Information private at no less a level than that by which we are bound.

 **6\. Cookies**  
We may send you a temporary cookie when you visit the Site. A cookie is a text-only string of information that we place in your computer's cookie file so that we can remember who you are when you revisit the Site. We may use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of the Site. You are not obliged to accept the cookie from us and you have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser.

 **7\. International Transfers**  
Personal information collected may be stored and processed in any country in which we or our affiliates, suppliers, subsidiaries, or agents are located. By using RummyRoyal services, you consent to all national and international transfers of your Personal Information without limitation.

 **8\. Third-Party Practices**  
Although RummyRoyal does its best to work only with trustworthy online sites, RummyRoyal does not take responsibility for any information that you provide to third-party sites which link to or from the Site. This includes, but is not limited to, affiliate sites and advertisers. Since these third-party sites are not operated by RummyRoyal, we take no responsibility for their privacy policies, if any. We recommend that you read their privacy policy before submitting any information to their website.

 **9\. Consent to Security Review**  
We reserve the right to conduct a security review at any time to validate your identity, age, the registration data provided by you, and to verify your use of RummyRoyal services and your financial transactions for potential breach of this Privacy Policy, the End User Agreement or any applicable law. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you authorize us, our staff, affiliates, subsidiaries, agents, and suppliers to use your Personal Information and to disclose your Personal Information to third parties for the purposes of validating the information you provide to us in the course of using the Services including, where necessary, the transfer of information outside of your country. Security reviews may include but are not limited to ordering a credit report and/or otherwise verifying the information you provide against third party databases. In addition, to facilitate these security reviews, you agree to provide such information or documentation as we may request.  
RummyRoyal reserves the right to use software to determine whether other active processes operating on your hardware represent a threat to the RummyRoyal System, either by using artificial intelligence to play the Games or by altering the RummyRoyal Software.

 **10\. Consent to Privacy Policy**  
By visiting the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy and we encourage you to periodically review it. Your continued use of the RummyRoyal Services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Policy, your only remedy is to discontinue use of RummyRoyal's services.

 **Disclaimer:**  
RummyRoyal does not assume liability for any events beyond our direct control. Despite RummyRoyal’s best efforts to maintain your privacy, due to the nature of the technology and software, we cannot guarantee, nor do we represent that there will be error-free performance as regards to the privacy of your personal information. RummyRoyal will not be liable for any indirect, incidental, consequential, or punitive damages relating to the use or release of Personal Information.

For further assistance, feel free to contact us.
